thuzi.com 2011-07-29

# Privacy

**PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT**

Updated and Effective June 1, 2010

Thuzi, L.L.C. (“Thuzi” or “We” or “Us”) is concerned with your privacy and your understanding of how your personal information may be collected, viewed, analyzed and used in conjunction with any of Thuzi’s websites or hosted applications (collectively the “Services”). This Privacy Policy only applies to Thuzi, L.L.C. and our Services. We have customers who use our Services as well so you may encounter our Services on one of our Thuzi hosted websites or those of our customers, or via a social networking website. The intent of this policy is to document how your personal information may be gathered and used by Thuzi. By using our Services you consent to the collection of your personal information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. Please note that it is likely that you will use our Services on or through links on a social networking site. Thuzi encourages all of our users to review privacy policies on any site where you may be sharing your personal information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and contact us if you have any questions.

**PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU**

Our Services may attempt to collect information through a number of different methods. In many cases we collect information that you provide directly when interacting with our Services. When using our Services you may be offered the chance to submit your own information such as your name, email address, sex, birth date, hobbies or other items of interest. We may also be able to collect some of that information from social networking systems where you are using our Services. We may also collect information about you from other public sources, companies or individuals. In addition to the information about yourself, you may also be providing information during the usage of the Services such as in surveys, contests or other submissions. Our services may also collect aggregate information about our users.

You should also be aware that it is standard practice to collect web based browser information that helps us to improve our Services. Examples of browser based information may include information such as referring sites, website visit statistics, entry pages, exit pages and your IP address and other information available in this manner. We may also collect information regarding the usage of our Services.

Thuzi attempts to protect personal information that it collects, but these measures are not failsafe. In general we attempt to prevent the misuse of any information we collect.

**CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13**

Thuzi does not knowingly request or collect information from children under the age of 13. If you are under 13 we ask that you not use our Services, or if you are in the care of a child under the age of 13 we ask that you prevent them from using our Services. If we learn that we have inadvertently collected information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you feel that we might have information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at info@thuzi.com. For children ages 13 to 18, we strongly recommend gaining parental approval prior to sending any personal information or using our Services.

**USAGE OF COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS**

“Cookies,” are a commonly used concept on the Internet designed to store user information such as their preferences when visiting a website. We may use Cookies to improve our Services and make your web experience more personal or more convenient, but they may also be used to collect usage statistics. Web browsers contain settings allowing you to control the use of cookies and whether you want to accept them. In some cases, eliminating cookie access may make it impossible to access certain functions of our Services. It is also possible that we, or a third party advertising company may also use or provide a pixel tag, clear gif, or beacon to help manage and optimize our ability to measure the usage of our Services and to provide better online advertising. Web beacons interact with cookies to provide better information on web usage. Currently we use services provided by Yahoo, so you should review their privacy policy at http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/details.html.

**USAGE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

We may use the personal information we collect to provide entertainment or value added services. Thuzi does not provide personally identifiable information to third party advertisers but may provide categorical information in order to post third party advertisements. The information may also be used to further personal communication through the sending of messages to you. Such messages or direct communication may be used to respond to comments, deliver notifications, or to send promotional information. You may always opt-out of those deliveries by following the opt-out instructions on the communication, or disconnecting our Services within the social networking website according to their standard procedures.

Thuzi may disclose information about you to its partners as part of our Services, in order to communicate with you and to provide you with advertising and promotional information as well as to improve your experience with our Services. We do not provide this information to our partners with an independent right for distribution.

Thuzi may also access, preserve and disclose any information we have about our users if required to do so by law, or in a good faith belief that such access or disclosure is reasonable necessary to avoid liability, to comply with legal process or to protect our rights and property or that of our partners or the general public. Thuzi is not required to contest the validity of any search warrant, subpoena or other similar governmental request.

**TRANSFER OF INFORMATION**

We reserve the right to transfer your personal information in the event of a transfer of ownership of Thuzi via an acquisition, company merger or otherwise.

**CUSTOMER POLICY**

Thuzi strongly encourages our customers to add language to their privacy policies that refer to the use of third party service providers or their products. Thuzi also strongly recommends that our customers provide information and opt-out instructions for their visitors. Our Services often contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites.

**CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**

Thuzi may make changes to this policy from time to time to keep it updated with our Services as well as emerging technologies or usage patterns on the Internet. We will post an effective date along with this policy in all cases.

**ABOUT THUZI, L.L.C.**

Thuzi, L.L.C. is a Florida Limited Liability Company and may be contacted for further information at info@thuzi.com.
